you know it's been a while since we
checked on Jack let's see how the guy's
doing now that he's back out of the
nursing home and making videos we're
ready to wrap our ribs they're at 165.
we're putting the meaty side down onto
the butter and sauce Jack you just got
out of the nursing home from what your
fourth or fifth stroke and you're making
a rack of ribs
on a stick of butter come on guy maybe
this is just a one-time thing let's
check another recipe that he's posted
since he's been out there we go
look how cheesy that is Jack that is
enough cheese to clog three people's
arteries what are you doing
you know what let's to forget about what
Jack is doing in the present and go to
the Past a time when Jack was still
getting his channel off the ground and
one of those things he thought would
help him launch his channel was product
reviews for As Seen On TV kitchen
gadgets this is one such video Jack's
review of our product you've probably
heard of the Magic Bullet before we
begin as always don't forget to like And
subscribe we just passed 500 not too
long ago and are slowly inching our way
towards that thousand Mark and every
little bit helps and I really do mean it
when I say every little bit helps the
prophecy didn't say anything about it
waking up this soon and it's happening
too fast so the more people we get the
longer we can put it off for please
welcome to the show Jack scalfani here
and you're cooking with Jack and this is
the episode you've been waiting for
you've been asking or should I say
you've been nagging it's the most
requested product review show it's
called the Magic Bullet God look at that
goatee man oh
should I
no but
no but first there's some things
happening to the show I wanna I wanna
bring you up on number one the show's
coming out with a new channel it's
called Jack on the go it's still food
related okay so you're still gonna get
all that yumminess but you're gonna be
with me on the go you all have been very
adamant that I check out this Jack on
the go channel so I will do just that in
the near future I promise from what I've
heard by some of the comments that you
guys have left it is Jack in the wild
more natural Jack something that's
unscripted not prompted like the cooking
show is so I'm definitely going to have
to check that out I got the brand new
iPod Nano the way it does the video and
all that it's really cool God the iPod
Nano I
I never had one I didn't even know it
could record video when I check out this
channel I'm going to need to look at
some of the earliest videos that he has
on there to see just how bad the quality
is go on over there and subscribe
because if you go and subscribe to Jack
on the go Channel I'm gonna be giving
somebody a free uh thing of sauce
I need to go subscribe I'm doing it
right now uh I don't care that this
video came out in 2009 Jack if you still
have a free sauce to hand out to
somebody
please I'm desperate some of you have
posted the recipe or a Mock recipe of
what Jack's Barbecue Sauce may have
tasted like so again that that could be
a very near future video should I tweet
at Jack that I just subscribed to Jack
on the go so maybe he'll restart the
sweepstakes and I can finally get a
bottle please Jack now let's do it let's
review the Magic Bullet
is that how you spell omelette I guess
it is it's one of those words that you
don't really see spelled out very
frequently so
all right before we do The Omelette
let's take a quick look at the
infomercial and see how they made The
Omelette any chance of getting a real
breakfast how about an omelette I'll
just take a couple eggs
how many you want anybody that grew up
with a lot of Public Access television
probably saw these infomercials a good
handful of times okay we'll just pop
this on now watch I'm chopping the ham
and veggies grating the cheese and
whipping the eggs ah in three seconds
and that's why the Magic Bullet became I
don't have the actual like statistics on
it but I'm pretty confident in saying it
was probably one of the best selling as
seen on TV kitchen gadgets of that
decade even probably partially now
what's really cool about this is this
has little legs so it doesn't fall over
while you're trying to put your eggs in
there yeah that's really cool Jack
two eggs right
that's right the guy wanted everything
in his remember so we're gonna do that
we're gonna give him just what he asked
for two eggs I don't recall ever seeing
Jack crack an egg before did he just
punch his egg open
two eggs right
that's right the guy wanted everything
in his remember so we're gonna no no he
cracked to the first egg open with the
second egg through the shell across the
room and then broke open the second egg
with his fist by punching it
there's your breakfast right there so
I'm gonna put it on
okay and she did it for three two counts
of three so we're gonna go one two three
one two three
that first set of three was not three
seconds maybe the second one was but you
and I both know you went faster on that
first one so if he says anything about
oh well I did it for the recommended
amount of time
no you didn't and that's what she did
and that was it so let's cook that up
and I'll bring it right back and we'll
take a look and see how it how it looks
you're watching the Cooking with Jack
show we'll be right back right after
this message are we gonna get a Jack's
sauces infomercial I'm pretty sure I've
seen enough of them by now to recite it
by heart let's see hey Jack scalfani
here here to tell you about my line of
sauces it's called the best barbecue
sauce you'll ever taste there it is hey
how you doing jack scalfana here to tell
you about my line of sauces it's called
the best barbecue sauce you'll ever
taste it's so good we made a hot one
there it is damn it it's so good we made
a hot one there it is damn I
think I know the second part oh
if that's not great enough
if that's not great enough something
something we made the best teriyaki
sauce you'll ever taste bam I'm pretty
sure that's the next part if that's not
good enough we made the best heraki
sauce you'll ever taste bam dang it I
was so close what's up next what's uh uh
barbecue sauce hot sauce teriyaki sauce
Gourmet Seas no I'm
is it Gourmet seasoning and to make it
even better we just released the best
gourmet seasoning you'll ever taste ah
it is
dang it by the time Jack is in the
hospital with his next stroke from all
the unhealthy stuff he continues to make
I'm going to have this infomercial
memorized I promise you guys go to
thebestsauces.com 100 guarantee we do
free shipping anywhere in the United
States go to thebestos.com I'll be there
waiting for you I wish you were there
waiting for me Jack but you're you don't
sell your sauces on your website anymore
I found the other day an old video of
his that had a listing for the sauce
that linked to a Walmart page
unfortunately it said it was out of
stock but it was 15
for a barbecue sauce and we're talking
about he probably bottled up another
open bottle of sweet baby rays through
some more ketchup and garlic in there
and called it his own sauce
in this economy
and now back to the cooking with Jack
show here's what I want to show you okay
this isn't even done cooking inside yet
this has been hard to cook well then
cook it for longer
if it's not done cooking yet and having
a hard time cooking cook it for longer
or put it in a bigger pan because that's
very clearly a very thick omelette and
if the pan was larger it would have more
space to spread out in you know I know
I'm burning the bottom of this already
Jack yeah you'd burn the bottom of your
omelets regardless of whether or not the
pan was too small so I'm taking it out
now but I mean it's not even fully
cooked on the inside okay
and
are you
are you blaming the magic bullet for you
not being able to cook an omelette are
you is that what you're telling me is
the Magic Bullet is the reason that you
can't cook an omelette by some miracle
when you put the eggs into that little
Gadget it somehow changed the
composition of the egg so they don't
cook normally like they would for you
and The Omelette isn't cooking and it's
all the magic bullet's fault not yours
because you don't know apparently how to
cook a basic omelette but this little
piece of plastic and Metal
its fault
oh Jack doesn't cook well
so I'm Gonna Roll this out
I guarantee we've already burnt the
outside
and look it's runny on the inside
and burnt on the outside look at that
that is not burnt Jack when he said it
was burnt I was expecting black that
isn't burnt that's just brown crispy egg
on the bottom of an omelette I most
omelettes I've seen in my life look that
color on the bottom look at that it
doesn't even cook well it doesn't even
cook well
the
object that's made for blending things
together
didn't cook well my guy
you just don't know how to cook eggs you
are the man who is so lazy that one of
your recipes on your channel is putting
eggs and omelette ingredients in a
Ziploc bag and boiling them because you
don't know how to make eggs properly
throw about five or six cherry tomatoes
in there they're the ones I like because
they've got all the flavor a little bit
of garlic a little bit of jalapeno
throwing an onion a little bit of
cilantro don't forget the blade just
takes a second to put on we're gonna add
tomatoes thing of garlic
okay so he added five tomatoes in the
infomercial and our friend Jack here put
in three along with that that clove of
garlic is about three times as big maybe
two and a half times as big as the clove
of garlic that they put in in the
infomercial not only is Jack
simultaneously overcrowd routing the
container with too much garlic he's also
undercrowding the container with not
enough tomatoes
little bit onions
in fact I'll I'll help it along I'm
going to break this in half says no no
complaining that I use too big of the
size of onion
we're gonna do jalapeno that jalapeno
slices
significantly thicker than what they
used
and we're gonna do a little bit of
break off some of this cilantro put a
little cilantro in there that's about
the same amount of cilantro just knowing
him I'm surprised Jack did not throw in
a block of cheese just for good measure
okay
now I expect this one to pass
this is going to be an incredible salsa
if this works that might be worth it for
me
here we go and he did it for three
seconds here we go
one two
three
and okay that was about the same amount
of time that they gave it in the
infomercial so if he complains about the
time spent on this
he's technically Justified I don't want
to give him that fact but yes he is
technically justified in saying that he
gave them about the same amount of time
I can already tell that he probably
should have blended it for longer but
there's a bunch of other factors that
could have come into play as well how
ripe the tomatoes and jalapeno is just
how soft everything is going into it is
also going to contribute to you know how
easily it chops up especially with
something like salsa where it's going to
be a partially liquid consistency exact
same ingredients
all right take a look
wow
why doesn't that look the same a few
more seconds and it probably would have
been fine you might have to shake it up
a little bit because it looks like you
got a piece of garlic stuck right on the
little pivot axle of the blade so it
wouldn't even be able to touch that
unless you moved it a tiny bit more time
add more Tomatoes it'd probably be fine
also if there were more tomatoes in it
there would be more mass in there to be
pushing things around that aren't cut up
yet and get chopped up by the blades
that would be like me putting half an
inch of cheese into a blender but the
blender blade is raised off the bottom
like three quarters of an inch or an
inch I can't really complain all too
much about the blade not chopping all of
it because as it cuts the cheese it's
going to spread out more it's not going
to be that block anymore so as it
spreads out more it reduces the chance
of the already cut food coming into
contact with the blade it's all a matter
of filling up the volume of the
container here look there's even garlic
in there that's not even broken up
let's see what that is before I go
tasting this this looks nasty
to the
V half of the garlic clove out with the
chip I was waiting for him to take a
bite of it and say it's very garlicky
because you know that's exactly what
Jack would do we're gonna show you what
it looks like
come on look at that I should have used
five tomatoes I only use three this test
isn't 100 accurate but it still didn't
okay maybe it's gonna scroll up
doesn't even look like
it didn't even mix it well or not but it
still didn't what Jack it still didn't
want it we can kind of fill in the blank
here but guessing what's going on in
Jack's head and what he's about to say
next is a very dangerous game see what
it tastes like
smells good looks nasty
really hot
that was a lot of Hope anyone there
um
oh man
Jack's always had a very weird history
with the spice tolerance because some
stuff he'll throw in a bunch of like hot
pepper seasonings and things like that
and then other times like this he'll eat
a teeny tiny jalapeno and then he'll
have the whole
because it's too hot for his poor Widow
Tommy
it tastes nasty all it is is jalapeno
tomato and cilantro so you're saying
you're tasting the primary ingredients
of the salsa
well that's a good thing isn't it but I
want to see if this thing even works so
I'm gonna do exactly what they recommend
and we're gonna
we're gonna dice
our garlic in this okay do you mean you
want to see if this thing works it's
clearly been working the whole time
will that look like the infomercial
okay that is how it should look yeah
because you just put Garlic in there
Jack what do you what do you expect it
to do you expect it to not chop it at
all you've got the weirdest Baseline for
if a test is a pass or a fail with
products
okay last test here we go
we're gonna do cheese take cheese right
here okay I'm putting one in there one
in there I'm not cutting anything up
anymore so Jack is just openly admitted
that he's not cutting anything up
anymore so if this fails this is
entirely on him this is again not the
product's fault this is Jack not
understanding basic kitchen tool
requirements wow that's all I can say
I've never been so frustrated on an
episode as I am today that is the
biggest piece of garbage the Magic
Bullet don't don't even look at it are
you looking at it nope
it gets no more attention you act like
this poor little silver guy over here
murdered your family I'm not buying it
in fact I'm giving this one back to my
dad I'm glad I stole it from him I'm
glad because your dad probably knows how
to use it Jack and with that that is
going to do it for this episode thank
you all for watching make sure to like
And subscribe leave a comment down below
for any other Jack videos you want me to
take a look at or any other channels or
topics you'd like me to cover as always
thanks he offer support and sticking
around and hope to see you all in the
next one see ya
[Music]
foreign